whatsonwhen.com 2012-12-24

# Whats on When - Events, Attractions, Festivals and Parties | World Events Calendar | whatsonwhen

John Wiley & Sons, Inc. and its related companies including but not limited to Whatsonwhen Limited (collectively, "Wiley") recognize the importance of protecting the information collected from Users in the operation of this website, and take reasonable steps to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of any information in accordance with this Privacy and Data Protection Policy. By submitting your information to Wiley you consent to the practices described herein. 

Wiley will seek to ensure that any identifiable personal information it collects during the registration and purchasing processes will be adequate, relevant and not excessive for purposes of operating this website or any of the services operated hereunder and it will be kept accurate and up-to-date based on information provided. Unless we have received your consent, or as expressly provided herein, Wiley will not disclose any personal information identifying users to any third party except where necessary in connection with services provided by appropriate intermediaries, who will be required to comply with the confidentiality provisions of this policy. In addition, Wiley may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in order to comply with the law or requests by law enforcement agencies, to enforce our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property or safety of our Web site, users or others. In the event that all or substantially all of the business or assets of relating to this Web site are sold or otherwise assigned to another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity. Personal information and any other communications or information supplied to Wiley may be used by Wiley for internal business and research purposes and to help enhance and develop our websites.

If you provide Wiley with your postal address, you may receive periodic catalogs from Wiley, or other notices containing information about new products and services or upcoming events. On occasion, Wiley may make its postal mailing address lists available to other companies who it believes may have products and services of interest to Wiley's customers. If you do not wish to receive postal mailings from Wiley, its imprints, or third-party organizations, please let us know via phone, fax, mail, or [email](http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/Section/id-301456.html). Please provide us with your exact name and postal address and state which lists you wish to be removed from so that we can be sure your information is removed from those mailing lists.

If use of an electronic product, feature or service offered by Wiley on this website requires a User to provide a name and password or other personally identifiable information, the User will have the option to opt in or out of providing such information and using the product, feature or service. 

Wiley may disclose to carefully chosen third parties navigational and transactional information in the form of anonymous, aggregate usage statistics (including "page views" on this website and the products herein) and demographics but only in forms that do not reveal a User's identity or confidential information, except as required by law, as needed in connection with legal proceedings, or unless we have received your consent.

Cookies are small bits of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are when you return. Cookies remember information about your activities on the site and enable the operator of the site to make your visits more enjoyable or customize your experience. We may use cookies in a variety of ways, such as to collect information to help us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. We don't use cookies to collect and store individually-identifiable information. You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. 

We also participate in TACODA Audience Networks (TAN) to optimize the advertisements you see. TACODA's privacy policy can be found [here.](http://www.tacoda.co.uk/notice/privacy_policy.html)

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

Tacoda's cookie statement can be found [here](http://www.tacoda.co.uk/notice/faq_privacy.html)

Links may be provided from this website to other third party websites. In using such links, Users should be aware that each third party website is subject to its own privacy and data protection policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. In addition, third parties may be placing and reading cookies in the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk or using web beacons to collect information in the course of ads being served on this website. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy and data protection policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. Wiley does not take responsibility for the privacy policies of, and usage of, personal information collected by others including, without limitation, those of any partner or affiliate.

You should be aware that identifiable personal information--such as your name or e-mail address--that you voluntarily disclose that are accessible to other Users (e.g. on bulletin boards or in chat areas) could be collected and disclosed by others. Wiley cannot take any responsibility for such collection and disclosure.

Please note that Wiley's Privacy and Data Protection Policy is reviewed periodically. Wiley reserves the right to modify its Privacy and Data Protection Policy at any time without notice. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page. Your continued use of this website will be deemed conclusive acceptance of such modification. Any comments or questions concerning this policy should be addressed by entering your comments through our [Contact Us](http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/Section/id-301456.html) page. If at any point you wish to access your personal information to (1) change your preferences, (2) review the accuracy, or (3) correct, supplement or modify your information, you may either select the [Contact Us](http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/Section/id-301456.html) page as set forth above, or make in a written request to John Wiley & Sons, Inc., 111 River Street, Hoboken, NJ 07030-5774. If you wish to modify your shopping account, you can do it directly in the [My Account](http://www.wiley.com/marketbasket.cgi?viewaccount) section.
